A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1994-2011
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1994-2011
The Library of Virginia
37424, 41166, 42221, 43155, 43715, 45555, 52152
25 cu. ft. (26 boxes)
Virginia Dept. of Environmental Quality. Office of the Director.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Department of Environmental Quality, Office of the Director, 629 East Main Street., Richmond, VA 23240. Accession 37424 transferred 21 June 2000; Accession 41166 transferred 5 May 2004; Accession 42221 transferred 27 September 2005; Accession 43155 transferred 2 April 2007; Accession 43715 transferred 18 April 2008; Accession 45555 transferred 10 June 2011; Accession 52152 transferred 15 November 2017.
Biographical Information
The Dept. of Environmental Quality was created by an act of the General Assembly (effective April 1, 1993) by consolidating the programs, functions, staff, facilities, assets, and obligations of the State Water Control Board, the Dept. of Air Pollution Control (State Air Pollution Control Board), the Dept. of Waste Management (Virginia Waste Management Board), and the Council on the Environment. The director of the department is appointed by the Governor. Directors include: Richard N. Burton (1993-1994); Peter W. Schmidt (1994-1996); Thomas L. Hopkins (1996-1998); Dennis H. Treacy (1998-2001); David A. Johnson (2002); Robert G. Burnley (2002-2006); and David K. Paylor (2006-present).
It is the policy of the Dept. of Environmental Quality to protect the environment of Virginia in order to promote the health and well-being of the Commonwealth's citizens by assisting in the effective implementation of state policies aimed at conserving the Commonwealth's natural resources and protecting its atmosphere, land and waters from pollution; coordinating permit review and issuance of procedures to protect all aspects of the environment; establishing and implementing a pollution prevention program to reduce the impact of pollutants; establishing procedures for and undertaking long-range environmental program planning and policy analysis; conducting comprehensive evaluations of the Commonwealth's environmental protection programs; providing for public education programs; developing uniform administrative systems to ensure coherent environmental policies; coordinating with federal agencies on environmental issues, such as environmental impact statements; promoting environmental quality through public hearings, permitting, inspection, monitoring and enforcement to enhance, preserve and protect Virginia's natural, scenic and historic environment; and advising the Governor and the General Assembly on matters relating to environmental quality.
Scope and Content
Records, 1994-2011, consisting of the correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Environmental Quality. These records include correspondence, memoranda, reports, weekly reports, speeches, meeting records and reference materials that document the planning, establishment, direction and implementation of agency programs, policies and procedures.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Correspondence and subject files, 1994-1996 [Accession 37424]
Series II: Correspondence and subject files, 1998-2001 [Accession 41166]
Series III: Correspondence and subject files, 1998-2002 [Accession 42221]
Series IV: Correspondence and subject files, 1995-2004 [Accession 43155]
Series V: Correspondence and subject files, 2002-2006 [Accession 43715]
Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, 2000-2005 [Accession 45555]
Series VII: Correspondence and subject files, 2006-2011 [Accession 52152]
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 37424], 1994-1996., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes). (Box 1-7)
  - Subseries A. 1995 Legislation - General Assembly
    - DEQ Agency proposals (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - DEQ Issues Assessment Supplemental Report (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Congressman Herbert Bateman (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Congressman Rick Boucher (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Congressman Thomas J. Bliley (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Congressman Robert Goodlatte (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Congressman James P. Moran (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Congressman L.F. Payne (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Senator Charles Robb (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Senator John W. Warner (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Congressman Norman Sisisky (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Congressman Frank R. Wolf (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Legislation, All (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Senator Hunter Andrews (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Senator Robert L. Calhoun (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Senator Joseph V. Gartlan, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Senator Virgil Goode, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Senator R. Edward Houck (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Senator Janet D. Howell (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Senator Madison Marye (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Senator Frank W. Nolen (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Senator Thomas K. Norment, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Senator H. Russell Potts, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Senator Jackson E. Reasor, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Senator Ed Robb (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Senator Elliot Schewel (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Senator Walter A. Stosch (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Senator Malfourd Trumbo (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Senator William C. Wampler, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Delegate Thomas G. Baker, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Delegate Robert B. Ball (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Delegate I. Vincent Behm, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Delegate W.W. Ted Bennett (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Delegate Robert S. Bloxom (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Delegate Whitt Clement (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Delegate Howard E. Copeland (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Delegate Elmo G. Cross, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Delegate Glenn Croshaw (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Delegate John J. "Butch" Davies (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Delegate Creigh Deeds (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Delegate George W. Grayson (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Delegate Raymond R. "Andy" Guest, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Delegate Phillip Hamilton (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Delegate Jay Katzen (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Delegate Alan E. Mayer (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Delegate William C. Mims (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Delegate Harvey Morgan (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Delegate Tayloe Murphy, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Delegate Clarence "Bud" Phillips (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Delegate Kenneth R. Plum (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Delegate W. Roscoe Reynolds (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Delegate Frank M. Ruff (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Delegate Victor Thomas (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Delegate Beverly J. Sherwood (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Delegate Frank Wagner (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Delegate Leo Waldrup (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Delegate John Watkins (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Delegate Peter T. Way (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Delegate S. Vance Wilkins (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Lobbying - Industry correspondence (Box 1, Folder 60-64)
  - Subseries B. State Agency Correspondence, 1994-1995
    - Accounts (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Attorney General Office (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Council on Information Management (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Dept. Conservation and Recreation (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Dept. of Emergency Services (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Dept. of Employee Relations Counselors (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Dept. of General Services (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Dept. of Health (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - JLARC Study (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Division of Legislative Services (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Dept. of Planning and Budget (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Dept. of State Internal Auditor (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Dept. of Transportation (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Dept. of Treasury (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Virginia Institute of Marine Sciences (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Virginia Water Resources Research Center (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Virginia Resources Authority (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Virginia Review (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Subseries C. Peter W. Schmidt Files, 1994-1998
    - Innsbrook lease (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - DEQ Internal moves (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson lighting and Brass works (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - JLARC waste facility report (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Privatization (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sanifill, Landfill (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Sartomer Chemical (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Standing (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Strike Force recommendations (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - DEQ Staff input regarding Strike Force (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Texaco lubricants (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Citizens board (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Joint board (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Budget (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Agency activity based budget submission (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Executive budget (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Issues assessment presentation (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Enforcement (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - External affairs (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - OIS (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Underground storage tanks (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Vegetative waste (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Waste tires (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Agency vehicles (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - VPEDS permitting (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Va. Water quality assessment report (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - EPA Superfund (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous EPA (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - EPA Air (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - EPA Emissions trading (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - EPA Richmond I/M rule (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - EPA Northern Virginia I/M rule (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - EPA Title V (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Governor/Cabinet, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, All staff, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Staff, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, OSNR, 1995 January-February (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, OSNR, 1995 March-May (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, OSNR, 1995 June-August (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, OSNR, 1995 September-October (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, OSNR, 1995 November-December (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 January (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 February (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 March (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 April-May (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 June-July (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 August (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 September (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 October (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1995 November-December (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Appointments, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Complimentary, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Government-Cabinet, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Meeting records, 1994 October-November (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Meeting records, 1994 December (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, OSNR, 1994 May-August (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, External, 1994 June-July (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, External, 1994 October-November (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, External, 1994 December (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Controlled, 1994 September-December (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Appointments, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Meeting records, 1995 January (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Meeting records, 1995 February (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Meeting records, 1995 March-April (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Meeting records, 1995 May-June (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Meeting records,1995 July-August (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Meeting records, 1995 September (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Meeting records, 1995 October (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Meeting records, 1995 November (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Meeting records, 1995 December (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 January-February (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 March (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 April (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 May (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 June-July (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 August (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 September (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 October (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, External, 1995 November-December (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1994 October (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1994 December (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 January (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 February (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 March (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 April (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 May (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 June (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 July (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 September (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 October (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 November (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1996 January (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1996 February (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1996 March (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 1996 April (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Proposal to serve as Financial Advisor by Evensen Dodge Inc., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Proposal to serve as Financial Advisor by First Albany Corp., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Proposal to serve as Financial Advisor by O'Brien Partners Inc., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Coastal Zone Resources Management Program, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Flood file, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Frito Lay relocation, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Labs, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Equipment, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Emergency response fund, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Innovative technology program, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Operation Spruce Up, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Permit fee program, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Permit process working group, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Voluntary remediation, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Strategic planning session, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - VWF conservation award, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Tributary strategy, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Report to Senate finance, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Regulation review, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Regional offices, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Southeast Compact Commission, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18-28)
- Series II: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 41166], 1998-2001., Extent: .45 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Requested input from staff, 1998 May-June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Requested input from staff, 1998 July-December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Speeches and talking points, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Speeches and talking points, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Speeches and talking points, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Speeches and talking points, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Working notes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Series III: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 42221], 1998-2002., Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 1-11)
  - Correspondence, Controlled, Instructions and sample or form letters (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Controlled, 1999 January-February (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Controlled, 1999 April (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Controlled, 1999 May-June (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Controlled, 1999 July-August (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Controlled, 1999 September-October (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Controlled, 1999 November-December (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Treacy, Dennis, Travel reimbursement, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Strategic Plan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, 1999 January (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, 1999 February (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, 1999 March (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, 1999 April (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meetings, 1999 May (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Meetings, 1999 June, Dennis Treacy (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Meetings, 1999 June (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, 1999 June, Strategic planning (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meetings, 1999 July (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Meetings, 1999 August (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, 1999 September (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, 1999 October (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, 1999 November (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, 1999 December (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1999 January-February (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1999 March (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1999 April (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1999 May-August (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999 September-December (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2000 January-March (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2000 April-May (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2000 June (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2000 July (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2000 August-September (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2000 October (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2000 November-December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 2001 January-February (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 2001 March-April (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2001 May-June (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 2001 July (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2001 July-August (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 2001 September (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 2001 October (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 2001 October-December (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, 1998 July (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 1998 August (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Meetings, 1998 September (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, 1998 October (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, 1998 November (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Meetings, 1998 December (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Legislation, Virginia, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Legislation, Federal, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Federal, EPA, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Treacy, Dennis, Travel reimbursements, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Pfiesteria Response Plan, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Total Maximum Daily Loads (TMDL), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Y2K, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, A-E, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, F-I, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, L-S, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, T-Z, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and Associations, A-H, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and Associations, O-Z, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 1998 January-March (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 1998 April-May (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998 June-August (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998 October-December (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Accomplishments, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gilmore transition, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Government and Cabinet, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, All Staff, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Staff, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Management meetings, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, 1998 January-February (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, 1998 March-April (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, 1998 April (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Meetings, 1998 May (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Meetings, 1998 June (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Thomas L. Hopkins, 1998 January-March (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1998 March-April (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998 May-June (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998 July (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1998 August-October (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1998 November-December (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 January-February (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 April-May (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 June (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 July (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 August (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 September-October (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 November (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Constituent/OSNR, 1998 December (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 January (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 February (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 March (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 April (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 May (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 June (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 July (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 August (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 September (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 October (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 November (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 December (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Accomplishments, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Federal legislators, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - State legislators, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, EPA, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, A-B, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, C-E, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, Hurricane Dennis, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, Hurricane Floyd, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, F-H, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, I-L, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, JLARC Toxics Database Study, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, M-T, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies, U-Z, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and Associations, A-I, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and Associations, I-O, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and Associations, S-U, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and Associations, V-Z, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Weekly reports, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)